sparkprofit.com 2017-10-05

# Terms of Service

PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING THE SITE AND USING THE SERVICES YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU ARE ACCESSING THE SITE OR USING THE SERVICES ON BEHALF OF AN ENTITY OR BUSINESS, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE THE AUTHORITY TO BIND SUCH ENTITY OR BUSINESS TO THESE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU OR THE ENTITY DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS SITE OR THE SERVICES. 

SITE TERMS OF SERVICE

We shall not be liable for any loss of profit, data loss, loss of production, depletion of goodwill or any indirect loss, costs or expenses whatsoever arising out of your use of our Website or your use of our services on our Website. 

We are not responsible for the content or reliability of linked Websites, and we do not necessarily endorse the views expressed within them. Linking should not be taken as an endorsement of any kind. We cannot guarantee that these links will work all of the time and we have no control over the availability of linked pages. 

The trade marks, logos and service marks shown on our Website, unless otherwise specified, are our trade marks. No rights are granted to use any of them without our prior written consent. 

Any infringement of our rights will result in appropriate legal action. 

We give no warranty regarding the ownership of any intellectual property either in the contents of this Website or in any other sites with which we may be linked. 

SPARKPROFIT PRIVACY STATEMENT

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE 

Thank you for visiting our website. 

This privacy statement states: 

  1. how we use cookies on our site; and
  2. how we collect, store and use information we collect about you when you use our website, whether as a guest or a registered user. Use of our website includes accessing, browsing or registering to use our website.

If you have any queries or comments relating to this privacy statement, please contact [team@sparkprofit.com](mailto:team@sparkprofit.com). 

Please read this privacy statement carefully before you start to use our website, as it will apply to your use of our website. By using our website, you confirm that you accept this privacy statement and that you will comply with it. If you do not agree to this privacy statement, you should not use our website and the Network.

###  OTHER APPLICABLE TERMS 

To access or use the Network, you must read and abide by the Network Terms and Conditions which will apply available here. 

###  ABOUT US 

[https://sparkprofit.com](https://sparkprofit.com/) is a website operated by Nous Global Markets Limited ("We"). We are registered in the United Kingdom under company number 9085400,  our office address is Aldwych House, 71-91 Aldwych, London WC2B 4HN. 

###  CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT 

We may revise this privacy statement at any time by amending this page. 

Please check this page from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes we have made, as they are binding on you. 

###  HOW WE USE COOKIES 

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a high quality browsing experience and also allows us to improve our site. By continuing to browse the site, you agree to our use of cookies as we have outlined in this privacy statement. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer, if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. 

We use the following cookies: 

  * Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website.
  * Analytical/performance cookies. These cookies allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors to our website and see how visitors use our website. This cookie helps us to improve the way our website works.
  * Functionality cookies. These cookies are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences.
  * Targeting cookies. These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.

We have outlined the table below the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them: 

Cookie| Purpose| More information  
---|---|---  
JSESSIONID |  Functionality |  This allows us to make sure that when you want information from our servers that requires us to know it's you, you don't need to enter your name and password for each separate request.   
urlHistory |  Analytical |  Helps us learn about what pages you visited before first deciding to join Spark Profit, so that we can make sure all our website pages are useful and interesting.   
opts |  Analytical |  Helps us know who invited you to join Spark Profit and also what options you were given if we were testing an improved sign-up process.   
__utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmz, __utmv |  Analytical/Performance |  Placed by [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/), a third party analytics package we use to learn how people use our site. You can opt-out of Google Analytics by [installing their browser extension](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).   
__qca |  Analytical/Performance |  Placed by [Quantcast](http://quantcast.com/), a third party analytics package employed by our blog provider, [Wordpress](http://wordpress.com/). You can [learn more about their privacy policy](https://www.quantcast.com/how-we-do-it/consumer-choice/privacy-policy/).   
  
Please note that third parties may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies. If you do not want us to use cookies as we have outlined above, or if you change your mind after having consented to our use of cookies, you may delete and block cookies on this site via your browser. If you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) parts of our website may not work. 

###  INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT ABOUT YOU 

We may collect and process the following data about you: 

  * information that you provide by filling in forms on our website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our Network or posting material. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site;
  * if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
  * details of transactions you carry out through our site; and/or
  * details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for credit payment purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

We may also collect information about your computer (including your IP address, operating system and browser type) for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about your browsing actions and does not identify you. 

###  WHERE WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION 

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored, outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy statement. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

###  HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION 

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

  * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you;
  * to provide you with the Network (as defined in the Network Terms and Conditions in the Spark Profit application), any service described in the Network Terms and Conditions, information, services that you request from us and/or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;
  * to carry out our obligations arising from the Network Terms and Conditions entered into between you and us https://sparkprofit.com/app;
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * to notify you about changes to our Network (as defined in the Network Terms and Conditions).

If we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this. 

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by contacting us at [team@sparkprofit.com](mailto:team@sparkprofit.com). 

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users. We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce either our Network Terms and Conditions or this privacy statement https://sparkprofit.com/app. You have the right to access the information we hold about you. Please contact [team@sparkprofit.com](mailto:team@sparkprofit.com) if you have any questions, comments relating to our privacy statement or would like to request access to information we hold. 

###  APPLICABLE LAW 

If you are a consumer, please note that these terms of use, its subject matter and its formation, are governed by English law. You and we both agree that the courts of England and Wales will have non-exclusive jurisdiction. However, if you are a resident of Northern Ireland you may also bring proceedings in Northern Ireland, and if you are resident of Scotland, you may also bring proceedings in Scotland. 

If you are a business, these terms of use, its subject matter and its formation (and any non-contractual disputes or claims) are governed by English law. We both agree to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England and Wales.
